<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<demos><!--This is an autogenerated file, please do not modify-->
   <name>AutoActive MATLAB Toolbox</name>
   <type>toolbox</type>
   <icon>HelpIcon.DEMOS</icon>
   <website/>
   <description>AutoActive MATLAB Toolbox provides support for writing and reading AutoActive Archives (AAZ) of multiple sensor data and video records. The toolbox also includes support for data import from different sensor types (e.g. Garmin, GaitUp, Catapult) and formats (e.g. gpx, csv). 
AAZ archives can be created, viewed and synchronized in ActivityPresenter, and can be read and written in MATLAB and ActivityPresenter as well as Python. The AutoActive Research Environment Toolbox provides the connection between ActivityPresenter used for data exploration/viewing/time synchronization and MATLAB used for data pre- and postprocessing and data analysis.   
The toolbox uses ArchiveWriter and ArchiveReader to write and read AAZ archives, respectively. The toolbox supports the transformations necessary for converting between MATLAB formats and the AAZ storage formats, its behavior is like a struct element when using it in a MATLAB script. The toolbox is plugin based which means that the user can easly extend the toolbox to support their own use-cases by adding custom plugins. 

Key Features
- Import of sensor data from multiple sensor types and formats including videos
- Read and write AAZ archives from/to ActivityPresenter
- Convertion between AAZ formats and MATLAB formats
- Merging av data and video from multiple sensor systems for time synchronziation and data analysis/viewing
- Annotations</description>
   <demosection>
      <label>cross_country_skiing_IMU_and_video</label>
      <demoitem>
         <label>activityPresenter_cycles_examples</label>
         <type>other</type>
         <source>activityPresenter_cycles_examples</source>
         <file>examples/cross_country_skiing_IMU_and_video/html/activityPresenter_cycles_examples.html</file>
      </demoitem>
   </demosection>
</demos>